{
    "subject": "resource/Ryan_Baldacchino",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Leicester",
    "human_readable": "Ryan Baldacchino was born in Leicester.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8847622871398926,
            "question": "Where was Ryan Baldacchino born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6298322677612305,
            "question": "In what city did Ryan Baldacchino grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5153881907463074,
            "question": "What is Ryan Baldacchino known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4150100350379944,
            "question": "What is Ryan Baldacchino's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39534834027290344,
            "question": "Where does Ryan Baldacchino currently reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3566318154335022,
            "question": "Does Ryan Baldacchino have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3043574392795563,
            "question": "What are some of Ryan Baldacchino's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23527801036834717,
            "question": "Who are some of Ryan Baldacchino's close friends?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22810278832912445,
            "question": "What is Ryan Baldacchino's educational background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21753177046775818,
            "question": "What are Ryan Baldacchino's hobbies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ryan Baldacchino was born in Leicester.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8233_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Ryan Baldacchino's educational background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8233_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of Ryan Baldacchino's close friends?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8233_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Ryan Baldacchino's accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8233_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8233_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents provide information about a person named Ryan Baldacchino, and one of them mentions that he \"was born in Leicester\" (although it also mentions that his parents are Maltese and that he has Maltese parentage). This seems to confirm that Ryan Baldacchino was indeed born in Leicester."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the document titled \"29.txt\", which states that Ryan Lee Baldacchino was born on the 13th of January, 1981, in Leicester, Leicestershire, England."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}